sportsmansoutdoorsuperstore.com 2011-08-05

# Sportsmans Outdoor Superstore - Where Sportsmen & Outdoors Meet.

**Your Privacy**   
At _The Sportsmans Outdoor Superstore_ , we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide a more personalized shopping experience. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy. 

**What Information Do We Collect? How Do We Use It?**   
When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit-card number and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your orders and to notify you of your order status. 

You may voluntarily sign up to be informed about certain offers. For this service we need only an e-mail address, which we use to send the information you requested. 

When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address and e-mail address, so we can administer the contest and notify winners. 

We personalize your shopping experience by using your purchases to shape our recommendations about other merchandise that might be of interest to you. We also monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop the design and layout of the store. 

We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important changes to the Web site, new _The Sportsmans Outdoor Superstore_ services and special offers we think you'll find valuable. If you would rather not receive this information, please notify us. Make sure to notify us for each account or e-mail address you have left with us. 

**What About "Cookies"?**   
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do enable us to provide features such as 1-Click shopping and to store items in your shopping cart between visits. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use most of the features in our store, including placing items in your shopping cart and purchasing them. 

**Will _The Sportsmans Outdoor Superstore_ Disclose the Information it Collects to Outside Parties? **   
_The Sportsmans Outdoor Superstore_ does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others. We may choose to do so in the future with trustworthy third parties, but you can tell us not to by sending a blank e-mail message to [info@sportsmansoutdoorsuperstore.com](mailto:info@sportsmansoutdoorsuperstore.com). (If you use more than one e-mail address to shop with us, send this message from each e-mail account you use.) Also, _The Sportsmans Outdoor Superstore_ may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information. 

**In Summary**   
We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make shopping at _The Sportsmans Outdoor Superstore_ possible and to enhance your overall shopping experience. We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others. We may choose to do so in the future with trustworthy third parties, but you can tell us not to by sending a blank e-mail message to [info@sportsmansoutdoorsuperstore.com](mailto:info@sportsmansoutdoorsuperstore.com). 

**Your Consent**   
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by _The Sportsmans Outdoor Superstore_. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

**Tell Us What You Think**   
_The Sportsmans Outdoor Superstore_ welcomes your questions and comments about privacy. Please e-mail us at [info@sportsmansoutdoorsuperstore.com](mailto:info@sportsmansoutdoorsuperstore.com).
